http://www.planetozkids.com/privacy_policy.html

Home  |  Animals Myths & Legends  |  Ace
Detectives Mysteries  |  Ozzoom Games  |
Teacher Activities  |   Store  |
Search
The policies below are applicable to Ozkids.com and Planet Ozkkids.com
and other sites on the Internet owned and operated by Word Design Interactive
Pty. Ltd.
The Legal Stuff
By
using our website, you confirm that you agree to our terms
and conditions of use and the terms of our privacy policy, described
below. We also reserve the right, at our soul discretion, to make additions,
deletions, or other changes to our terms of use and privacy policy at
any time. It is your responsibility to periodically check these terms
for any changes. Continuing to use Planet Ozkids On-line following the
publishing of these changes means you accept the changes.
Sorry
about all the legal stuff but we have to protect our copyrighted material – and
most importantly, keep our website fun and safe to use for the kids
and their parents and teachers visiting this site.
Privacy Policy
We
recognise that parents are concerned about the privacy of their family
and especially the privacy of their children on-line.
We
do not require personal information from visitors before allowing them
to access any part of our website. Any requests for data are entirely
voluntary.
We
are trying to bring you the best on-line experience possible so we may
ask visitors to share information or submit details to register for
newsletters or enter competitions or to help us improve the site.  Children
under 18 should always seek permission from their parents or guardian
before transmitting any information.
We
are totally committed to the privacy of this information and will under
no circumstance release, sell, share or transfer information to third
parties.
As
we add more features and services to our site for your benefit and new
laws regarding the use of the Internet occur, we may have to update
this privacy policy. Rest assured we do not anticipate changing from
our philosophy of protecting the privacy of visitors to this site or
using in an inappropriate way information disclosed to us.
Visitor Tracking
We
do use software to track the total number of visitors to our site
and the number of visitors to each area of the site.  This information
only shows us which areas visitors enjoy most and helps us to improve
the site.  We do not extract personal information in this process.
This means the user remains anonymous to us.
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.
Use of Site
By
using this site, you signify your assent to the Word Design Interactive
Pty. Ltd. Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please
do not use our site.
Please
also read our Terms and Conditions
of Use.
If
you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact
us.
